Guide to the Seattle Design Commission Project Files 1968-1986
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Seattle Design Commission Project Files, 1968-1986; 9323-02
  - Alley Block 3, Palatine Hill Addition 070176.1, 1976 (Box-folder 19/16)
  - 17th Avenue Northeast / Northeast Naomi Place Triangle 070176.3, 1976 (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Rainier Square Pedestrian Concourse 070176.4, 1976 (Box-folder 19/18)
  - Seacrest Marina Feasibility Study 070176.6, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 19/19)
  - Westlake Project 070176.8, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 19/20)
  - Westlake Project 070176.8, 1979 (Box-folder 19/21)
  - Westlake Project 070176.8, 1978 (Box-folder 19/22)
  - Westlake Project 070176.8, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 19/23)
  - Traffic Signalization 070176.9, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 19/24)
  - Mount Baker Boulevard South 071576.2, 1976 (Box-folder 19/25)
  - 4th Avenue South Viaduct 080576.1, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - 8th Avenue Northwest 080576.5, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Northwest 59th Street and Northwest 60th Street Widenings 090276.1, 1976 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - North Greenwood Curbs and Gutters, Phases I, II, and III 090276.2, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - 24th Avenue Northwest Dock Improvements 090276.3, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Broadway UAB 091676.3, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Fire Signal, Station 24 091676.4, 1976 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Southwest Cloverdale Street Grading, etc. 091676.5, 1976 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Wheelchair Ramps 100776.3, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Leschi Neighborhood Improvement Program Plan 100776.5, 1976 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Seattle Central Business District - Exclusive Bus Lanes Draft Environmental Impact Statement 100776.7 B, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Fremont UAB 102176.5, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Riverview Neighborhood Improvement Program / South Delridge Neighborhood Improvement Program 110476.5 / 110476.6, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Montlake Boulevard 110476.9, 1976 (Box-folder 20/14)
  - West Woodland Neighborhood Improvement Program 120276.1, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - 43rd Avenue South 120276.7, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/16)
  - 4th Avenue and Battery 120276.12, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Pioneer Square Areaway Study 120276.13, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Pioneer Square Areaway Study 120276.13, 1976 (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Reservoir Protection 121676.1, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/20)
  - First Hill Neighborhood Improvement Program Lighting 121676.3, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/21)
  - Holman Road Northwest Widening 121676.4, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Montlake UAB, Phase I 010677.1, 1977 (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Metro Trolley Bus Overhead 010677.4, 1979 (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Metro Trolley Bus Overhead 010677.4, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Seattle Center Maintenance Levy Project / Directional Signing 010677.5, 1977 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Seattle Center Fun Forest 010677.6, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Woodland Park Improvements 012077.1, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - International District Community Center 012077.12, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - North Beacon Hill Neighborhood Improvement Program / South Park Community Development Block Grant 020377.3 / 020377.4, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Proposed Traffic Code Revisions 020377.6, 1977 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - 23rd Avenue West and West Gilman Bridge 021777.5, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Alley, Block 2, Webster's Madison Addition 021777.7, 1977 (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Pike Street Low Impact Development 021777.14, 1978 (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Pike Street Low Impact Development 021777.14, 1977 (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Rainier and Barton Signal Installation 030377.3, 1977 (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Airport Way South Viaduct (Over Argo Railroad Yards) / 4th Avenue South Viaduct 030377.6 - 030377.7, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 21/15)
  - Alley, Block 3, McLaughlin's Madrona Hill Addition 031777.7, 1977 (Box-folder 21/16)
  - Alley, Block 2, Kelsey's First Addition 031777.8, 1977 (Box-folder 21/17)
  - Mercer Corridor Immediate Action Program 031777.10, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 21/18)
  - Mercer Corridor Immediate Action Program 031777.10, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 21/19)
  - South Lucille Street Bridge 040777.2, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - South Lucille Street Bridge 040777.2, 1977 (Box-folder 22/2)